Oliver Otis Howard Papers M091 M091
George J. Mitchell Department of Special Collections & Archives, Bowdoin College Library, Brunswick, Maine 04011
- M91.4: Correspondence, western command period, May 1874-November 1888, M91.4; 10.5 linear feet
  - 1882 Sep 20 - 1882 Sep 26 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - 1882 Sep 27 - 1882 Sep 30 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - 1882 Oct 01 - 1882 Oct 09 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 1882 Oct 10 - 1882 Oct 13 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 1882 Oct 14 - 1882 Oct 31 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 1882 Nov 01 - 1882 Nov 07 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 1882 Nov 08 - 1882 Nov 10 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - 1882 Nov 11 - 1882 Nov 16 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 1882 Nov 17 - 1882 Nov 30 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 1882 Dec 01 - 1882 Dec 06 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 1882 Dec 07 - 1882 Dec 15 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 1882 Dec 16 - 1882 Dec 18 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - 1882 Dec 19 - 1882 Dec 26 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - 1882 Dec 27 - 1882 Dec 31 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - 1883 Jan 01 - 1883 Jan 07 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - 1883 Jan 08 - 1883 Jan 10 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - 1883 Jan 11 - 1883 Jan 14 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - 1883 Jan 15 - 1883 Jan 18 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - 1883 Jan 19 - 1883 Jan 21 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - 1883 Jan 22 - 1883 Jan 25 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - 1883 Jan 26 - 1883 Jan 29 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - 1883 Jan 30 - 1883 Jan 31 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - 1883 Feb 01 - 1883 Feb 07 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - 1883 Feb 08 - 1883 Feb 15 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - 1883 Feb 16 - 1883 Feb 18 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - 1883 Feb 19 - 1883 Feb 23 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - 1883 Feb 24 - 1883 Feb 28 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - 1883 Mar 01 - 1883 Mar 06 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - 1883 Mar 07 - 1883 Mar 12 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - 1883 Mar 13 - 1883 Mar 20 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - 1883 Mar 21 - 1883 Mar 25 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - 1883 Mar 26 - 1883 Mar 28 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - 1883 Mar 29 - 1883 Mar 31 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - 1883 Apr 01 - 1883 Apr 08 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - 1883 Apr 09 - 1833 Apr 11 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - 1883 Apr 12 - 1883 Apr 17 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - 1883 Apr 18 - 1883 Apr 24 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - 1883 Apr 25 - 1883 Apr 30 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - 1883 May 01 - 1883 May 03 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - 1883 May 04 - 1883 May 09 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - 1883 May 10 - 1883 May 18 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - 1883 May 19 - 1883 May 31 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - 1883 Jun 01 - 1883 Jun 05 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - 1883 Jun 06 - 1883 Jun 13 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - 1883 Jun 14 - 1883 Jun 27 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - 1883 Jun 28 - 1883 Jun 30 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - 1883 Jul 01 - 1883 Jul 08 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - 1883 Jul 09 - 1883 Jul 23 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - 1883 Jul 24 - 1883 Jul 31 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - 1883 Aug 01 - 1883 Aug 12 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - 1883 Aug 13 - 1883 Aug 20 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - 1883 Aug 21 - 1883 Aug 31 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - 1883 Sep 01 - 1883 Sep 06 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - 1883 Sep 07 - 1883 Sep 18 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - 1883 Sep 19 - 1883 Sep 30 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - 1883 Oct 01 - 1883 Oct 09 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - 1883 Oct 10 - 1883 Oct 13 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - 1883 Oct 14 - 1883 Oct 19 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - 1883 Oct 20 - 1883 Oct 26 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - 1883 Oct 27 - 1883 Oct 31 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - 1883 Nov 01 - 1883 Nov 07 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - 1883 Nov 08 - 1883 Nov 17 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - 1883 Nov 18 - 1883 Nov 23 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - 1883 Nov 24 - 1883 Nov 30 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - 1883 Dec 01 - 1883 Dec 07 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - 1883 Dec 08 - 1883 Dec 12 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - 1883 Dec 13 - 1883 Dec 20 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - 1883 Dec 21 - 1883 Dec 31 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - 1884 Jan 01 - 1883 Jan 05 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - 1884 Jan 06 - 1884 Jan 10 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - 1884 Jan 11 - 1884 Jan 16 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - 1884 Jan 17 - 1884 Jan 19 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - 1884 Jan 20 - 1884 Jan 24 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - 1884 Jan 25 - 1884 Jan 28 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - 1884 Jan 29 - 1884 Jan 31 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - 1884 Feb 01 - 1884 Feb 05 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - 1884 Feb 06 - 1884 Feb 10 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - 1884 Feb 11 - 1884 Feb 16 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - 1884 Feb 17 - 1884 Feb 21 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - 1884 Feb 22 - 1884 Feb 29 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - 1884 Mar 01 - 1884 Mar 03 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - 1884 Mar 04 - 1884 Mar 11 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - 1884 Mar 12 - 1884 Mar 31 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - 1884 Apr 01 - 1884 Apr 27 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - 1884 May 01 - 1884 May 08 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 1884 May 09 - 1884 May 31 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 1884 Jun 01 - 1884 Jun 09 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 1884 Jun 10 - 1884 Jun 18 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 1884 Jun 19 - 1884 Jun 30 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 1884 Jul 01 - 1884 Jul 21 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - 1884 Jul 22 - 1884 Jul 24 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - 1884 Jul 25 - 1884 Jul 31 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - 1884 Aug 01 - 1884 Aug 07 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - 1884 Aug 08 - 1884 Aug 19 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - 1884 Aug 20 - 1884 Aug 31 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - 1884 Sep 01 - 1884 Sep 11 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - 1884 Sep 12 - 1884 Sep 30 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - 1884 Oct 01 - 1884 Oct 20 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - 1884 Oct 21 - 1884 Oct 31 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - 1884 Nov 01 - 1884 Nov 07 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - 1884 Nov 08 - 1884 Nov 13 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - 1884 Nov 14 - 1884 Nov 19 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - 1884 Nov 20 - 1884 Nov 30 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - 1884 Dec 01 - 1884 Dec 09 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - 1884 Dec 10 - 1884 Dec 14 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - 1884 Dec 15 - 1884 Dec 23 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - 1884 Dec 24 - 1884 Dec 31 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - 1885 Jan 01 - 1885 Jan 08 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - 1885 Jan 10 - 1885 Jan 16 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - 1885 Jan 17 - 1885 Jan 23 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - 1885 Jan 24 - 1885 Jan 26 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - 1885 Jan 27 - 1885 Jan 31 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - 1885 Feb 01 - 1885 Feb 06 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - 1885 Feb 07 - 1885 Feb 10 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - 1885 Feb 11 - 1885 Feb 18 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - 1885 Feb 19 - 1885 Feb 25 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - 1885 Feb 26 - 1885 Feb 28 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - 1885 Mar 01 - 1885 Mar 05 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - 1885 Mar 06 - 1885 Mar 12 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - 1885 Mar 13 - 1885 Mar 16 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - 1885 Mar 17 - 1885 Mar 21 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - 1885 Mar 22 - 1885 Mar 31 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - 1885 Apr 01 - 1885 Apr 11 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - 1885 Apr 12 - 1885 Apr 18 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - 1885 Apr 19 - 1885 Apr 30 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - 1885 May 01 - 1885 May 10 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - 1885 May 11 - 1885 May 15 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - 1885 May 16 - 1885 May 19 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - 1885 May 20 - 1885 May 25 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - 1885 May 26 - 1885 May 31 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - 1885 Jun 01 - 1885 Jun 14 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - 1885 Jun 15 - 1885 Jun 22 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - 1885 Jun 23 - 1885 Jun 30 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - 1885 Jul 01 - 1885 Jul 08 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - 1885 Jul 09 - 1885 Jul 11 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - 1885 Jul 12 - 1885 Jul 20 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - 1885 Jul 21 - 1885 Jul 27 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - 1885 Jul 28 - 1885 Jul 31 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - 1885 Aug 01 - 1885 Aug 04 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - 1885 Aug 05 - 1885 Aug 09 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - 1885 Aug 10 - 1885 Aug 13 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - 1885 Aug 14 - 1885 Aug 21 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - 1885 Aug 22 - 1885 Aug 27 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - 1885 Aug 28 - 1885 Aug 31 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - 1885 Sep 01 - 1885 Sep 03 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - 1885 Sep 04 - 1885 Sep 08 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - 1885 Sep 09 - 1885 Sep 16 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - 1885 Sep 17 - 1885 Sep 20 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - 1885 Sep 21 - 1885 Sep 24 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - 1885 Sep 25 - 1885 Sep 30 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - 1885 Oct 01 - 1885 Oct 07 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - 1885 Oct 08 - 1885 Oct 13 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - 1885 Oct 14 - 1885 Oct 19 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - 1885 Oct 20 - 1885 Oct 23 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - 1885 Oct 24 - 1885 Oct 30 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - 1885 Nov 01 - 1885 Nov 05 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - 1885 Nov 06 - 1885 Nov 12 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - 1885 Nov 13 - 1885 Nov 17 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - 1885 Nov 18 - 1885 Nov 20 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - 1885 Nov 21 - 1885 Nov 26 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - 1885 Nov 27 - 1885 Nov 30 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - 1885 Dec 01 - 1885 Dec 04 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - 1885 Dec 05 - 1885 Dec 10 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - 1885 Dec 11 - 1885 Dec 13 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - 1885 Dec 14 - 1885 Dec 19 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - 1885 Dec 20 - 1885 Dec 24 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - 1885 Dec 25 - 1885 Dec 31 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - 1886 Jan 01 - 1886 Jan 07 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 1886 Jan 08 - 1886 Jan 14 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 1886 Jan 15 - 1886 Jan 23 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 1886 Jan 24 - 1886 Jan 31 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 1886 Feb 01 - 1886 Feb 04 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 1886 Feb 05 - 1886 Feb 09 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 1886 Feb 10 - 1886 Feb 12 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - 1886 Feb 13 - 1886 Feb 17 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 1886 Feb 18 - 1886 Feb 28 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - 1886 Mar 01 - 1886 Mar 04 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - 1886 Mar 05 - 1886 Mar 06 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - 1886 Mar 07 - 1886 Mar 11 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - 1886 Mar 12 - 1886 Mar 16 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - 1886 Mar 17 - 1886 Mar 19 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - 1886 Mar 20 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - 1886 Mar 21 - 1886 Mar 22 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - 1886 Mar 23 - 1886 Mar 25 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - 1886 Mar 26 - 1886 Mar 31 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - 1886 Apr 01 - 1886 Apr 02 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - 1886 Apr 03 - 1886 Apr 06 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - 1886 Apr 07 - 1886 Apr 09 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - 1886 Apr 10 - 1886 Apr 14 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - 1886 Apr 15 - 1886 Apr 20 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - 1886 Apr 21 - 1886 Apr 26 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - 1886 Apr 27 - 1886 Apr 30 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - 1886 May 01 - 1886 May 06 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - 1886 May 07 - 1886 May 10 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - 1886 May 11 - 1886 May 13 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - 1886 May 14 - 1886 May 19 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - 1886 May 20 - 1886 May 24 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - 1886 May 25 - 1886 May 31 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - 1886 Jun 01 - 1886 Jun 04 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - 1886 Jun 05 - 1886 Jun 10 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - 1886 Jun 11 - 1886 Jun 16 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - 1886 Jun 17 - 1886 Jun 20 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - 1886 Jun 21 - 1886 Jun 23 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - 1886 Jun 24 - 1886 Jun 26 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - 1886 Jun 28 - 1886 Jun 30 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - 1886 Jul 01 - 1886 Jul 07 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - 1886 Jul 08 - 1886 Jul 14 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - 1886 Jul 15 - 1886 Jul 21 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - 1886 Jul 22 - 1886 Jul 27 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - 1886 Jul 28 - 1886 Jul 31 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - 1886 Aug 01 - 1886 Aug 05 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - 1886 Aug 06 - 1886 Aug 10 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - 1886 Aug 11 - 1886 Aug 14 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - 1886 Aug 15 - 1886 Aug 18 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - 1886 Aug 19 - 1886 Aug 23 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - 1886 Aug 24 - 1886 Aug 29 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - 1886 Aug 30 - 1886 Aug 31 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - 1886 Sep 01 - 1886 Sep 05 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - 1886 Sep 06 - 1886 Sep 08 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - 1886 Sep 09 - 1886 Sep 11 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - 1886 Sep 12 - 1886 Sep 16 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - 1886 Sep 17 - 1886 Sep 21 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - 1886 Sep 22 - 1886 Sep 26 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - 1886 Sep 27 - 1886 Sep 30 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - 1886 Oct 01 - 1886 Oct 04 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - 1886 Oct 05 - 1886 Oct 09 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - 1886 Oct 10 - 1886 Oct 11 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - 1886 Oct 12 - 1886 Oct 17 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - 1886 Oct 18 - 1886 Oct 26 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 1886 Oct 27 - 1886 Oct 31 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 1886 Nov 01 - 1886 Nov 06 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 1886 Nov 07 - 1886 Nov 11 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 1886 Nov 12 - 1886 Nov 15 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - 1886 Nov 16 - 1886 Nov 20 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - 1886 Nov 21 - 1886 Nov 24 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - 1886 Nov 25 - 1886 Nov 30 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 1886 Dec 01 - 1886 Dec 03 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 1886 Dec 04 - 1886 Dec 06 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 1886 Dec 07 - 1886 Dec 13 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 1886 Dec 14 - 1886 Dec 19 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - 1886 Dec 20 - 1886 Dec 23 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - 1886 Dec 24 - 1886 Dec 27 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - 1886 Dec 28 - 1886 Dec 31 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - 1887 Jan 01 - 1887 Jan 09 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - 1887 Jan 10 - 1887 Jan 12 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - 1887 Jan 13 - 1887 Jan 17 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - 1887 Jan 18 - 1887 Jan 21 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - 1887 Jan 22 - 1887 Jan 25 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - 1887 Jan 26 - 1887 Jan 31 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - 1887 Feb 01 - 1887 Feb 02 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - 1887 Feb 03 - 1887 Feb 06 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - 1887 Feb 07 - 1887 Feb 10 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - 1887 Feb 11 - 1887 Feb 12 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - 1887 Feb 13 - 1887 Feb 17 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - 1887 Feb 18 - 1887 Feb 21 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - 1887 Feb 22 - 1887 Feb 25 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - 1887 Feb 26 - 1887 Feb 28 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - 1887 Mar 01 - 1887 Mar 06 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - 1887 Mar 07 - 1887 Mar 09 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - 1887 Mar 10 - 1887 Mar 14 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - 1887 Mar 15 - 1887 Mar 16 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - 1887 Mar 17 - 1887 Mar 19 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - 1887 Mar 20 - 1887 Mar 23 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - 1887 Mar 24 - 1887 Mar 28 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - 1887 Mar 29 - 1887 Mar 31 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - 1887 Apr 01 - 1887 Apr 07 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - 1887 Apr 08 - 1887 Apr 15 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - 1887 Apr 16 - 1887 Apr 19 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - 1887 Apr 20 - 1887 Apr 24 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - 1887 Apr 25 - 1887 Apr 28 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - 1887 Apr 29 - 1887 Apr 30 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - 1887 May 01 - 1887 May 09 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - 1887 May 10 - 1887 May 18 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - 1887 May 19 - 1887 May 23 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - 1887 May 24 - 1887 May 31 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - 1887 Jun 01 - 1887 Jun 07 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - 1887 Jun 08 - 1887 Jun 16 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - 1887 Jun 17 - 1887 Jun 24 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - 1887 Jun 25 - 1887 Jun 30 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - 1887 Jul 01 - 1887 Jul 06 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - 1887 Jul 07 - 1887 Jul 11 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - 1887 Jul 12 - 1887 Jul 14 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - 1887 Jul 15 - 1887 Jul 20 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - 1887 Jul 21 - 1887 Jul 28 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - 1887 Jul 29 - 1887 Jul 31 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - 1887 Aug 01 - 1887 Aug 03 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - 1887 Aug 04 - 1887 Aug 10 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - 1887 Aug 11 - 1887 Aug 15 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - 1887 Aug 16 - 1887 Aug 23 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - 1887 Aug 24 - 1887 Aug 28 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - 1887 Aug 29 - 1887 Aug 31 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - 1887 Sep 01 - 1887 Sep 05 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 1887 Sep 06 - 1887 Sep 08 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 1887 Sep 09 - 1887 Sep 11 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 1887 Sep 12 - 1887 Sep 15 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 1887 Sep 16 - 1887 Sep 22 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 1887 Sep 23 - 1887 Sep 26 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 1887 Sep 27 - 1887 Sep 29 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 1887 Sep 30 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 1887 Oct 01 - 1887 Oct 06 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - 1887 Oct 07 - 1887 Oct 11 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - 1887 Oct 12 - 1887 Oct 15 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - 1887 Oct 16 - 1887 Oct 20 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - 1887 Oct 21 - 1887 Oct 25 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - 1887 Oct 26 - 1887 Oct 31 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - 1887 Nov 01 - 1887 Nov 04 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - 1887 Nov 05 - 1887 Nov 08 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - 1887 Nov 09 - 1887 Nov 11 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - 1887 Nov 12 - 1887 Nov 17 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - 1887 Nov 18 - 1887 Nov 21 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - 1887 Nov 22 - 1887 Nov 24 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - 1887 Nov 25 - 1887 Nov 30 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - 1887 Dec 01 - 1887 Dec 04 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - 1887 Dec 05 - 1887 Dec 09 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - 1887 Dec 10 - 1887 Dec 14 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - 1887 Dec 15 - 1887 Dec 19 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - 1887 Dec 20 - 1887 Dec 21 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - 1887 Dec 22 - 1887 Dec 25 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - 1887 Dec 26 - 1887 Dec 31 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - 1888 Jan 01 - 1888 Jan 05 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - 1888 Jan 06 - 1888 Jan 11 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - 1888 Jan 12 - 1888 Jan 20 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - 1888 Jan 21 - 1888 Jan 26 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - 1888 Jan 27 - 1888 Jan 31 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - 1888 Feb 01 - 1888 Feb 08 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - 1888 Feb 09 - 1888 Feb 17 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - 1888 Feb 18 - 1888 Feb 24 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - 1888 Feb 25 - 1888 Feb 29 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - 1888 Mar 01 - 1888 Mar 05 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - 1888 Mar 06 - 1888 Mar 08 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - 1888 Mar 09 - 1888 Mar 17 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - 1888 Mar 18 - 1888 Mar 20 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - 1888 Mar 21 - 1888 Mar 25 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - 1888 Mar 26 - 1888 Mar 31 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - 1888 Apr 01 - 1888 Apr 06 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - 1888 Apr 07 - 1888 Apr 10 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - 1888 Apr 11 - 1888 Apr 16 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - 1888 Apr 17 - 1888 Apr 27 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - 1888 Apr 28 - 1888 Apr 31 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - 1888 May [undated] (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - 1888 May 01 - 1888 May 06 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - 1888 May 07 - 1888 May 10 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - 1888 May 11 - 1888 May 16 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - 1888 May 17 - 1888 May 21 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - 1888 May 22 - 1888 May 24 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - 1888 May 25 - 1888 May 28 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - 1888 May 29 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - 1888 May 30 - 1888 May 31 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - 1888 Jun 01 - 1888 Jun 05 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1888 Jun 06 - 1888 Jun 10 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 1888 Jun 11 - 1888 Jun 13 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 1888 Jun 14 - 1888 Jun 17 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 1888 Jun 18 - 1888 Jun 22 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 1888 Jun 23 - 1888 Jun 30 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 1888 Jul 01 - 1888 Jul 05 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - 1888 Jul 06 - 1888 Jul 12 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - 1888 Jul 13 - 1888 Jul 14 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 1888 Jul 15 - 1888 Jul 18 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - 1888 Jul 19 - 1888 Jul 31 [loose] (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - 1888 Jul 19 - 1888 Jul 31 [signature] (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - 1888 Aug 01 - 1888 Aug 06 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - 1888 Aug 07 - 1888 Aug 10 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - 1888 Aug 11 - 1888 Aug 17 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - 1888 Aug 18 - 1888 Aug 22 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - 1888 Aug 23 - 1888 Aug 28 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - 1888 Aug 29 - 1888 Aug 31 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - 1888 Sep 01 - 1888 Sep 04 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - 1888 Sep 05 - 1888 Sep 09 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - 1888 Sep 10 - 1888 Sep 16 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - 1888 Sep 17 - 1888 Sep 22 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - 1888 Sep 23 - 1888 Sep 30 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - 1888 Oct 01 - 1888 Oct 04 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - 1888 Oct 05 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - 1888 Oct 06 - 1888 Oct 12 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - 1888 Oct 13 - 1888 Oct 17 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - 1888 Oct 18 - 1888 Oct 22 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - 1888 Oct 23 - 1888 Oct 31 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - 1888 Nov 01 - 1888 Nov 07 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - 1888 Nov 08 - 1888 Nov 12 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - 1888 Nov 13 - 1888 Nov 16 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - 1888 Nov 17 - 1888 Nov 18 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - 1888 Nov 19 - 1888 Nov 20 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - 1888 Nov 21 - 1888 Nov 30 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- M91.5: Correspondence, eastern command period, December 1888-November 1894, M91.5; 9.25 linear feet
  Correspondence, mostly letters received by Howard (letters sent are contained in letterpress volumes, M91.7) dealing with Howard's service as Commander of the Division of the Atlantic (1888-91) and the Department of the East (1891-94). Incomplete indexes (M91.9) are available for use in Special Collections. Besides official business correspondence, there are letters concerning Howard's personal appearances and Republican Party politics.
  - 1888 Dec 01 - 1888 Dec 05 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - 1888 Dec 06 - 1888 Dec 11 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - 1888 Dec 12 - 1888 Dec 13 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - 1888 Dec 14 - 1888 Dec 16 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - 1888 Dec 17 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - 1888 Dec 18 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - 1888 Dec 19 - 1888 Dec 21 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - 1888 Dec 22 - 1888 Dec 24 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - 1888 Dec 25 - 1888 Dec 26 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - 1888 Dec 27 - 1888 Dec 28 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - 1888 Dec 29 - 1888 Dec 31 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - 1889 Jan 01 - 1888 Jan 03 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - 1889 Jan 04 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - 1889 Jan 05 - 1889 Jan 06 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - 1889 Jan 07 - 1889 Jan 09 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - 1889 Jan 10 - 1889 Jan 11 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - 1889 Jan 12 - 1889 Jan 14 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - 1889 Jan 15 - 1889 Jan 16 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - 1889 Jan 17 - 1889 Jan 20 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - 1889 Jan 21 - 1889 Jan 23 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - 1889 Jan 24 - 1889 Jan 25 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - 1889 Jan 26 - 1889 Jan 28 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - 1889 Jan 29 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - 1889 Jan 30 - 1889 Jan 31 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - 1889 Feb 01 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - 1889 Feb 02 - 1889 Feb 04 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - 1889 Feb 05 - 1889 Feb 06 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - 1889 Feb 07 - 1889 Feb 08 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - 1889 Feb 09 - 1889 Feb 11 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - 1889 Feb 12 - 1889 Feb 13 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - 1889 Feb 14 - 1889 Feb 15 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 1889 Feb 16 - 1889 Feb 20 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 1889 Feb 21 - 1889 Feb 22 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 1889 Feb 23 - 1889 Feb 26 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 1889 Feb 27 - 1889 Feb 28 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - 1889 Mar 01 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 1889 Mar 02 - 1889 Mar 04 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - 1889 Mar 05 - 1889 Mar 06 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - 1889 Mar 07 - 1889 Mar 10 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - 1889 Mar 11 - 1889 Mar 12 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - 1889 Mar 13 - 1889 Mar 15 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - 1889 Mar 16 - 1889 Mar 19 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - 1889 Mar 20 - 1889 Mar 23 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - 1889 Mar 24 - 1889 Mar 31 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - 1889 Apr 01 - 1889 Apr 03 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - 1889 Apr 04 - 1889 Apr 11 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - 1889 Apr 12 - 1889 Apr 14 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - 1889 Apr 15 - 1889 Apr 16 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - 1889 Apr 17 - 1889 Apr 18 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - 1889 Apr 19 - 1889 Apr 21 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - 1889 Apr 22 - 1889 Apr 23 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - 1889 Apr 24 - 1889 Apr 25 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - 1889 Apr 26 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - 1889 Apr 27 - 1889 Apr 30 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - 1889 May 01 - 1889 May 02 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - 1889 May 03 - 1889 May 04 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - 1889 May 05 - 1889 May 08 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - 1889 May 09 - 1889 May 10 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - 1889 May 11 - 1889 May 13 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - 1889 May 14 - 1889 May 15 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - 1889 May 16 - 1889 May 17 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - 1889 May 18 - 1889 May 21 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - 1889 May 22 - 1889 May 24 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - 1889 May 25 - 1889 May 28 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - 1889 May 29 - 1889 May 31 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - 1889 Jun 01 - 1889 Jun 02 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - 1889 Jun 03 - 1889 Jun 04 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - 1889 Jun 05 - 1889 Jun 08 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - 1889 Jun 09 - 1889 Jun 12 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - 1889 Jun 13 - 1889 Jun 17 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - 1889 Jun 18 - 1889 Jun 21 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - 1889 Jun 22 - 1889 Jun 26 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - 1889 Jun 27 - 1889 Jun 31 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - 1889 Jul 01 - 1889 Jul 04 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - 1889 Jul 05 - 1889 Jul 08 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - 1889 Jul 09 - 1889 Jul 11 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - 1889 Jul 12 - 1889 Jul 15 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - 1889 Jul 16 - 1889 Jul 20 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - 1889 Jul 21 - 1889 Jul 24 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - 1889 Jul 25 - 1889 Jul 31 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - 1889 Aug 01 - 1889 Aug 04 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - 1889 Aug 05 - 1889 Aug 10 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - 1889 Aug 11 - 1889 Aug 17 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - 1889 Aug 18 - 1889 Aug 23 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - 1889 Aug 24 - 1889 Aug 31 (Box 23, Folder 55)